qservers.net 2015-07-06

# QServers.net | Nigeria Web Hosting Free Domain Names Nigeria Web Hosting Nigeria Cheap Reliable

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 14, 2012.  
The last update before that was on October 26, 2010.

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to QServers.net. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Additionally, QServers.net adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles as agreed to and set forth by the United States Department of Commerce and the European Union ("EU"), http://export.gov/safeharbor/. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our website.

QServers.net reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting on-line at this location. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. You may identify whether QServers.net has revised this Privacy Policy by noting the "Effective Date" above. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

Types of Information Collected

In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.  
  
Personal Information

When you order services through QServers.net, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form to us to allow us to process your order, provide you with the services you order from us, and to provide ongoing technical support for your account. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, phone number, and address). By purchasing our services, you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information. Your personal information will be kept only as long as we need it for the purposes for which we collected it, or as permitted by law.

After you have ordered our services, we may be in communication with you about your account. These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality services that are responsive to your needs. As a result, we may maintain information about our communications with you for future use.

QServers.net shall only process Personal Information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by the individual. To the extent necessary for those purposes, QServers.net shall take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use.

Disclosure of Personal Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide service. In the event that this policy changes, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit the disclosure of your information to third parties for any purpose other than your ordering and ongoing use of our services. For sensitive information, affirmative or explicit (opt in) choice will be given if the information is to be disclosed to a third party or used for a purpose other than previously authorized.

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personal Information to others. We do provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties. We and our service partners use your Personal Information to operate our sites and to deliver our services.

Occasionally, QServers.net may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personal Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personal Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use QServers.net services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that QServers.net in good faith believe to be unlawful.

QServers.net may also use the Personal Information collected to contact customers regarding important changes to our site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers through email by sending your request at support@QServers.net.

Non-Personal Information

QServers.net collects tracking data when users visit our websites. Whenever you request a page through your browser, navigation data such as your IP address, browser and version, operating system, date and time and the site from which you came are stored in a log file. We use this data to analyze visitors' use of our site in order to make improvements to our site.

Disclosure of Non-Personal Information

QServers.net may share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with other business partners. We do not share any information with anyone that can identify an individual user.  
Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. QServers.net may use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers help file.

Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The QServers.net website uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. When entering Personal Information, we strongly recommend an SSL-enabled web browser.

Our Commitment to Safe Harbor

QServers.net believes in protecting your privacy. When we collect personal information from you on our website, we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union. QServers.net will regularly review our privacy promises, to ensure that we are in compliance U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework.

Safe Harbor Enforcement

QServers.net uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this privacy policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible and in conformity with the Principles of Safe Harbor. Should you have any concerns please contact us with the information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal Information in accordance with the Principles.

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Access To Your Personal Information

You always have access to the information we have about you. To review and update your personal contact information, simply log into our client portal. You may also email support@QServers.net to have the information changed or do it yourself on your profile page.

Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or our compliance with the Safe Harbor principals, please contact us at:

QServers.net / Netbuilder Limited  
Attn: Legal Department  
5th Floor Centage Plaza,  
14 Allen Avenue  
Ikeja-Lagos

Email: support@QServers.net
